Natalia Stukan

40 Common Approach, Benfleet, Essex, SS73LA +44 (0) 7958602281 natalia.stukan@yahoo.com
http://stukanstudio.co.uk/

I'm a competent junior frontend developer. I particularly enjoy AngularJS, Polymer, JQuery and am fascinated by UX design.

During my previous roles working with Wordpress, Drupal, social media and CRMs (e.g. Salesforce), I've acquired a broad range of experience and strengthened my HTML, CSS and JavaScript knowledge as well as gained an understanding in the fundamentals of PHP, Angular, Polymer, AJAX, JSON and Git.

I've loved my journey in becoming a frontend developer and would be thrilled to have an opportunity to develop my career further.

Core Competencies

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, AngularJS, JQuery, Bootstrap, SASS, Polymer, Compass, Git version control
- · Wireframing: Balsamiq, basic Axure
- Operating systems: Windows, iOS, Basic Linux commands
- Dev enviroment: XAMPP, Sublime, Terminal, Git, CyberDuck
- CMS/CRM's: Drupal, Wordpress I tend to pick these up quickly, so what I don't know I can generally learn first time round
- An all round team player, I am capable of working to strict briefs and time constraints.
- · Fluent English, Russian, Mandarin

Relevant Experience

The Development Factory, Sydney (January 2015 - July 2015)

Junior Frontend Developer

- AngularJS sites support
- Flexbox and Polymer Frontend for CeBIT Australia 2015 social media digital display
- Custom built CRM using Polymer for Hello Social
- Polymer Frontend development for Cycling Australia greenfield project
- Polymer Frontend development for Baxter IP internal management tool
- Wireframing, responsive design and general site layouts for agency client sites
- Bootstrap, PHP, JSON POC project for a Counterfeit Guard tool for sunshadesevewear.com.au
- Facebook app styling for Shooters and Fishers Party (www.facebook.com/SFPAustralia/app_322187487985810)

<u>HudHost, Sydney</u> (November 2014 - December 2014)

Junior Frontend Developer

- Built dashboard interfaces with the Bootstrap responsive website framework
- · Email server dashboard, product control panels
- Responsive checkout pages

CAPA - Centre for Aviation, Sydney (April-November 2014)

Account Manager

- Selling delegate passes to international aviation summits
- Developing and maintaining databases using Salesforce
- Liaising with the company stakeholders, conference producers and sponsors

Ketchum Maslov, Moscow, Russia (July-October 2013)

Digital Specialist

- Managing social media presence of P&G Russia
- Creating digital marketing materials and social posts
- Client communication, user engagement reporting and statistic analysis

Other Experience

Freelance Translator (2007 - 2013)

- Translated for clients in many industries including IT, medicine and legal documentation. Projects of note include: English and Russian for Genius Products, Elekta UK, The Cayman Islands Taxation
- Subtitling for Chinese Television shows from Mandarin into Russian.

Education/Professional development

Google Code School

- Staying Sharp with AngularJS (May 2015).
- Shaping up with AngularJS (January 2015).

Treehouse

- Frontend Web Development (November-December 2014)
- PHP Development(January 2015)

Barnaul State Pedagogical University, Department of Linguistics, Barnaul, Russia (2003 - 2008)

- Graduated with honours.
- Acquired a Bachelor Degree in Linguistics.
- Acquired a Translator's Certificate.

More Information

References:

Paul Sharratt, MD of The Development Factory - (+61) 0400 426 454

LinkedIn:

http://www.linkedin.com/pub/natalia-stukan/75/45/355